Guide to the Picture File, 1600s-1979 and undated, bulk 1814-1950
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- People Series, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated, (22 boxes)
  - Ing--Negl, 1805-1967, 1800s, 1900s and undated
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (17 card photographs and 1 silhouette) (Folder M1235.2)
      Some images have been colored.
      Some images contain original signatures.
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (18 card photographs) (Folder M1235.3)
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (18 card photographs) (Folder M1235.4)
      These photographs come from 110 individual and group pictures of various members of the Lewis family who lived in Hampton, NH; Gainesville, AL and Columbus, MS; and of the allied families of Barry, Converse, Neilson and others.
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (18 card photographs) (Folder M1235.5)
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (10 card photographs) (Folder M1235.6)
    - Lewis, Wm. M. Collection, 1800s, (10 tintypes) (Folder M1235.7)
    - Lilly, E. J., E. J. Jr., and H. W., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1236)
    - Lincoln, Benjamin, undated, (7 engravings) (Folder M1237)
      One item removed to Box M05, Folder OV119, Oversize Subseries.
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1862, 1866, 1898 and 1800s, (5 engravings) (Folder M1238.1)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1864 and 1800s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 card photograph) (Folder M1238.2)
      One photograph, 1903, removed to Box MO5, folder OV122.
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1863 Apr. 23, (signed engraving) (Folder M1238.3)
      Removed to Carrell 211.
      Engraving is framed with a dated autograph addressed to Miss Adeline B. Marchant. Formerly in the Mary Duke Biddle home.
    - Lincoln, Abraham (on his deathbed), 1865 Apr. 14, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1239)
    - Lincoln, Mary (Todd), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1240)
    - Livingston, Robert R. (1746-1813), 1862, (engraving) (Folder M1241)
    - Livingstone, David, undated, (2 engravings and 1 clipping) (Folder M1242)
    - Locke, John, 1829 June 1, (engraving) (Folder M1243)
    - Locke, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1244)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1960, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 lithograph) (Folder M1245)
    - Lokke, Carl Ludwig, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1246)
    - Long, Huey Pierce, 1900s, (engraving)
      Includes a signed note.
      Removed to Box M05, Folder OV122, Oversize Subseries.
    - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1910 and 1800s, (1 black-and-white illustration and 1 postcard) (Folder M1247)
      The illustration is a copy of a painting of Longfellow. The postcard is a copy of a painting of Longfellow's three daughters.
    - Longstreet, James, circa 1860s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1248)
    - Longstreet, Maria Louise (Garland) and two of her children, 1800s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1249)
    - Longstreet, Nicholas, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1250)
    - Lowell, James Russell, 1934, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1251)
    - Lowell, James Russell, 1872 July 8 and 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M1252)
      Card photograph contains an original, dated signature.
    - Lowin, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1253)
    - Loyola, Ignatius, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1254)
    - Lucas, Ada M., 1902, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1255)
    - Lucas, Daniel Bedinger, undated, (engraving)
      Removed to Box M05, Folder 123, Oversize Subseries.
    - Lucas, J. B. C., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1256)
    - Lucas, James H. and his former residence, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M1257)
    - Luce, Stephen Bleecker, 1901 July, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1258)
    - Ludlow, Noah Miller, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1259)
    - Ludwig, Emil, 1900s, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1260)
      Illustration is a copy of a photograph from the back of a book cover.
    - Lumpkin, J. T., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1261)
    - Lymon, Emily Cunningham, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1262)
    - Lynch, Thomas, Jr., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1263)
    - Lyon, N., 1862, (engraving) (Folder M1264)
    - Lyons, Josephine, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1265)
    - McAdoo, William Gibbs, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Box 28, Folder M1266)
    - McCabe, Charles Cardwell, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1267)
    - McCabe, William Gordon, III, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1268)
    - McCall, George, Archibald, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1269)
    - McCalla, John Moore, 1800s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1270)
    - McCarthy, Justin, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1271)
    - McClellan, George B., 1861, circa 1860s, and 1800s, (6 card photographs and 5 engravings) (Folder M1272.1)
    - McClellan, George B., circa 1860s, (3 card photographs) (Folder M1272.2)
    - McClellan, George B., circa 1860s, (3 card photographs) (Folder M1272.3)
    - McCloskey, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1273)
    - McCook, Edward Moody, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1274)
    - McCulloch, Arthur Lee and Marion Edith, 1899, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1275)
    - McDonald, Flora, 1890, (card photograph) (Folder M1276)
    - McDonald, Joseph Ewing, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1277)
    - McGowan, Admiral Samuel, F. D. R., and Josephus Daniels, circa 1940s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1278)
    - McGowan, S. M., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1279)
      Includes a signed note addressed to Mrs. Pickins(?).
    - McGowan, Samuel, et al., 1891, 1800s, and 1900s, (12 black-and-white photographs and 2 card photographs) (Folder M1280)
      Eight images in the folder are from the "S. C. U. Law Class, 1891."
      Three photographs removed to Box M05, Folder OV124 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - McHenry, James, 1888, (2 engravings) (Folder M1281)
    - McIntosh, Lachlan, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M1282)
    - McKissick, A. F., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1283)
    - McLaws, Lafayette, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1284)
      Image comes from the scrapbook of Charles E. Jones.
    - MacRae, William, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1285)
      Transferred from the Hugh MacRae Mss.
    - McSwain, J. J., 1920, 1922, and 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1286)
    - McSwain, John Jackson, 1900s and 1936 Aug. 8, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1287)
      2 photographs removed to Box M05, Folder OV125 in the Oversize Series.
    - Macomb, Alexander, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1288)
    - Madison, Dorothea (Payne) Todd, 1872 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1289)
    - Madison, James, 1805, 1861, and 1800s, (4 engravings) (Folder M1290)
    - Madison, James, 1849, (engraving) (Folder M1291)
    - Madison, James (Bishop), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1292)
    - Magri, Countess Mercy Lavinia Warren (Bumpus), 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1293)
    - Magruder, John Bankhead, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1294)
    - Mahan, Alfred Thayer, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1295)
      Illustration is a photographic copy of an illustration from a book.
    - Malbone, Edward G., 1815, (2 engravings) (Folder M1296)
    - Mangum, Presley Jackson, Family, 1800s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1297)
      Folder contains birthdates and death dates of the pictured family members.
    - Mangum, Willie Person, undated, (1 black-and-white photograph, 1 card photograph, and 1 cased image) (Folder M1298)
      One item removed to Envelope C1 in the Cased Images Series.
    - Manning, John Hall, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M1299)
    - Manning, Peyton T., circa 1860s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1300)
    - Marion, Francis, 1852 and 1858, (2 engravings) (Folder M1301)
    - Marion, Francis, 1800s, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1302)
      Illustration is a photographic copy of a painting.
    - Mars, Mademoiselle (Anne Francoise Hippolyte Salvetat Boutet) (1779-1847), 1814, (2 engravings)
      French actress. Removed to Box M05, Folder 126, Oversize Subseries.
    - Marshall, John (1755-1835), 1863, (2 engravings) (Folder M1303)
    - Marshall, Thomas Riley, undated, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1304)
      One image contains an original signature.
      One item removed to Box M05, Folder OV127 in the Oversize Series.
    - Martin, Alexander (1740-1807), 1888, (engraving) (Folder M1305)
    - Martin, John Sanford ("Santford" Martin), 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1306)
    - Martin, Luther (c.1748-1826), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1307)
    - Marx, Karl, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1308)
    - Mary I, Queen of England and Ireland, 1827 Feb. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Box M05, Folder OV128,Oversize Subseries.
    - Mary, Queen of Scots, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1309)
    - Masaryk, Thomas Garrigue, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph)
      Czech politician. Removed to Box LG03, Folder OV129, Oversize Subseries.
    - Mason, Lucy Randolph, 1950, circa 1940s, and circa 1950s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1310.1)
    - Mason, Lucy Randolph, 1943 Feb., circa 1940s, and circa 1950s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1310.2)
    - Mason, Lucy Randolph, 1952 Mar., circa 1940s, and circa 1950s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1310.3)
    - Mason, Lucy Randolph, circa 1940s and circa 1950s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1310.4)
    - Matas, Rudolph, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1311)
    - Maury, Thomas F., 1800s, (3 card photographs) (Folder M1312)
    - Meigs, Montgomery Cunningham, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1313)
    - Meigs, Return Jonathan (1764-1824), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1314)
    - Memminger, C. G.(?), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1315)
    - Mencken, Henry Louis, 1900s, (5 color photographs) (Folder M1316)
    - Merrick, John and W. G. Pearson, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1317)
    - Merritt, William Calhoun, et al., 1893, (card photograph) (Folder M1318)
      Photograph of the Class of 1893 of the North Carolina Conference, Methodist Episcopal Church, South.
    - Methodist Episcopal Church, South: Judicial Board, 1934-1938, circa 1930s, (black-and-white photograph)
      Single sheet containing nine portraits.
      Removed to Box M05, Folder OV130, Oversize Subseries.
    - Metternich, von, Klemens Wenzel Nepomuk Lothar, Prince, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1319)
    - Middleton, Arthur, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1320)
    - Milledge, John, circa 1920s Oct. 25, (lithograph) (Folder M1321)
    - Miller, Samuel F., 1889, (engraving) (Folder M1322)
    - Miller, Walter McNab (Mrs.), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1323)
    - Milner, Sir Alfred, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1324)
    - Mirabeau, Octave Henri Marie, undated, (engraving) (Box 29, Folder M1325)
    - Mitchell, Donald Grant, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1326)
    - Mitchell, O. M., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1327)
    - Mommsen, Theodor, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1328)
    - Monroe, James, 1849 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1329)
      One item removed to Box M05, Folder OV131, Oversize Subseries.
    - Montefiore, Sir Moses, undated, (lithograph) (Folder M1330)
    - Montgomery, Richard, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1331)
    - Montgomery, Richard (alias James Thompson), 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1332)
      Transferred from the C. C. Clay Papers.
    - Moore, A. M., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1333)
    - Moore, Aaron McDuffie, 1900s, (negative)
      Item removed to Negatives Series.
    - Moore, Alfred, 1889, (engraving) (Folder M1334)
    - Moore, Colleen, 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1335)
    - Moore, Henry, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1336)
    - Moore, Thomas, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1337)
    - Mordaunt, Charles, Third Earl of Peterborough and First Earl of Monmouth of the second creation, 1829 May 1, (engraving) (Folder M1338)
    - More, Sir John (circa 1453-1530), 1826 Dec. 1, (engraving)
      Item removed to Box M05, Folder OV132, Oversize Subseries.
    - More, Sir Thomas, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1339)
    - Morgan, Daniel, 1862 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1340)
    - Morgan, John Hunt, 1800s, (2 card photographs and 1 engraving) (Folder M1341)
      Engraving includes a list of important events in the life of John Hunt Morgan.
    - Morgan, John Tyler, 1879, (card photograph) (Folder M1342)
    - Morris, George Pope, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1343)
    - Morris, J. B., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1344)
    - Morris, Robert, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1345)
    - Morris, Robert, Jr. (1734-1806), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1346)
    - Morrison, Herbert Stanley, Baron Morrison of Lumbeth, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1347)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1348)
    - Mosby, John Singleton, 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M1349)
    - Moseley, William, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1350)
    - Moultrie, William, 1862 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1351)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1800s, (engraving)
      Item removed to Box M06, Folder OV133, Oversize Subseries.
    - Mundy, Miss Nelly, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1352)
      Engraving is a copy of a painting.
    - Munford, Elizabeth Thorowgood (Ellis), 1895, (card photograph) (Folder M1353)
    - Munford, Frances (Bland), 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1354)
    - Munford, George Wythe, 1878, (card photograph) (Folder M1355)
    - Munford, Daughters of Geo. W. Munford and Margaret N. Tucker, 1901, (card photograph) (Folder M1356)
      Back of image contains biographical data about those pictured.
    - Munford, Robert B., 1873, (card photograph) (Folder M1357)
    - Munford, Thomas Taylor, 1914 and 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1358)
    - Munford, William, undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1359)
    - Munford, William Preston, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1360)
    - Murray, George (Sir) (1772-1846), 1831, (engraving) (Folder M1361)
    - Murray, Phillip, 1940 and 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1362)
    - Murray, William, First Earl of Mansfield, 1833 May 1, (engraving)
      Item removed to Box M06, Folder OV134, Oversize Subseries.
    - Myddelton or Middleton, Jane, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1363)
    - Napoleon II, King of Rome, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1364)
    - Napoleon III, Emperor of the French, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1365)
  - Native Americans (see Indians)
  - Neg-Negroes
    - Negley, James Scott, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1366)
  - Negroes (African Americans), circa 1870s-circa 1960s, 1800s and undated
    - "Away Down Among 'de Cotton and de Coons,'" Louisiana, U.S., 1898, (stereograph) (Box 29)
      Item removed to Stereographs Series.
    - Fifteenth Amendment Bringing his Crop to Town, 1800s, (stereograph)
    - "Georgia Negro Born into Slavery," 1800s, (black-and-white photograph)
      Item removed to Box LG03, Folder OV135, Oversize Subseries.
    - Man and woman, elegantly dressed in a formal portrait, circa 1870s, (tintype) (Folder M1367)
      Deteriorating, handle with care.
    - "Negro Collection," 1927, (20 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1368.1)
      Illustrations are copies of several different original formats, which comprise a collection of 101 prints of African American men and women of distinction.
      Some negatives available.
    - "Negro Collection," 1927, (20 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1368.2)
    - "Negro Collection," 1927, (20 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1368.3)
    - "Negro Collection," 1927, (20 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1368.4)
    - "Negro Collection," 1927, (21 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1368.5)
      Includes portrait and 8x10 copy of W. E. B. Dubois.
    - "Negro Drawing: Reconstruction North Carolina," 1800s, (clipping) (Folder M1369)
    - Pickaninnies, 1913, (postcard) (Folder M1370)
      Postcard is addressed and contains a signed note, complete with a stamp.
    - Sergeant, U.S. Army, circa 1860s, (colored tintype) (Folder M1371)
    - Tenants, 1800s, (3 black-and-white photographs and 1 card photograph) (Folder M1372)
      Transferred from the Reuben D. Bowen Mss.
    - Typical Negro Home, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1373)
    - Washington, Mabel, 1890, (card photograph) (Folder M1374)
  - Nel--Z, 1749-1968, 1900s and undated
    - Nelson, Horatio, Viscount Nelson, 1829 and 1884, (2 engravings) (Box 29, Folder M1375)
    - Newhouse, Samuel, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1376)
    - Niederinghaus, Frederick G., undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1377)
    - Nisbet, Eugenius Aristides, 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M1378)
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, and family, 1968 Nov. 6, (color illustration) (Folder M1379)
      Illustration is a reproduction of a color photograph.
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, and family, 1968, (postcard) (Folder M1380)
      Postcard was part of Nixon presidential campaign.
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1960 and undated, (black-and-white photograph and 1 lithograph) (Folder M1381)
      Lithograph removed to Box LG03, Folder OV136 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Noble, Marcus Cicero Stephens, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1382)
    - Norman, Newton Jones, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1383)
    - Norris, George William, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1384)
      Transferred from Harry Slattery Mss.
    - Norris, John E., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1385)
    - Norton, Fletcher, First Baron Grantley, 1782 June, (sketch) (Folder M1386)
    - Norwood, Thomas Manson, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1387)
    - Nott, Eliphalet, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1388)
    - Oaksmith, Appleton, 1861 and 1880, (1 card photograph and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1389)
    - O'Connell, Daniel (1775-1847), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1390)
    - Officers of the C. S. Army and Navy, undated, (black-and-white photograph)
      Photo is a collage of the officers of the C. S. Army and Navy with labels.
      Removed to Box LG03, Folder OV137, Oversize Subseries.
    - Ogilby, Lady, 1806 May 1, (engraving) (Folder M1391)
    - Oglethorpe, James, 1847 and 1800s, (4 engravings and 1 sketch) (Folder M1392)
      Two engravings removed to Box LG03, Folder OV138 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Older, Fremont, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1393)
    - Olmsted, Denison, 1847, (engraving) (Folder M1394)
    - Olney, Richard, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1395)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1396)
    - Osborne, Lord Sidney Godolphin, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1397)
    - Otis, James, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1398)
    - Page, Walter Hines, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1399)
    - Paget, William, First Baron Paget of Braudesert, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1400)
    - Pakenham, Sir Edward Michael and Sir Samuel Gibbs, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1401)
      Engraving is of a statue of the two men which can be found in St. Paul's Cathederal.
    - Palmer, Alexander Mitchell, 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M1402)
    - Palmer, B. H., 1874, (card photograph) (Folder M1403)
    - Parker, Alton Brooks, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1404)
    - Parr, Samuel, 1847, (engraving) (Box 30, Folder M1405)
    - Parrott, Enoch Greenleafe, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1406)
    - Patterson, Robert, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1407)
    - Paxton, Joseph, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1408)
    - Peabody, George, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1409)
    - Peace, B. H., 1931 Feb. 23, (black-and-white photograph)
      Includes a signed and dated note.
      Removed to Box LG03, Folder OV139 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Pearson, Thomas, 1803 Jan. 1, (engraving) (Folder M1410)
    - Peary, Robert Edwin, 1910, (black-and-white photograph)
      Includes signature which has become blurred.
      Photograph is of a bronze bust.
      Removed to Box LG03, Folder OV140 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Peel, Sir Robert, Second Baronet, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1411)
    - Peel, Sir Robert, First Baronet, 1834 and 1800s, (4 engravings) (Folder M1412)
    - Pelham, John, circa 1860s, (card photograph) (Folder M1413)
    - Pemberton, John C., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1414)
    - Pendleton, W. N., circa 1860s, (engraving) (Folder M1415)
      Transferred from the scrapbook of Charles E. Jones.
    - Penick, the Rt. Rev. Edwin A., et al., 1935 May 30, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1416)
      Folder also contains information about the photographs as well as the individuals within them and a newspaper story from the Raleigh News and Observer.
    - Penn, William (1644-1718), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1417)
    - Pennypacker, Samuel W., 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1418)
    - Perceval, John, Earl of Egmont, 1798 Nov. 24, (engraving) (Folder M1419)
    - Perceval, Spencer, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1420)
    - Perkins, Thomas Lee, 1900s, (4 sketches) (Folder M1421.1)
      This folder contains four copies of the same sketch.
    - Perkins, Thomas Lee, 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1421.2)
    - Perkins, William Robertson, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1422)
    - Perkins, William Robertson, 1900s, (5 sketches) (Folder M1423)
      All five images are exact copies of a sketch by Sid Hydeman.
    - Perrow, Eber Carle, 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs and 3 negatives) (Folder M1424)
      The three negatives were removed to folder N22 in the Negatives Series.
    - Perry, B. F., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1425)
    - Pershing, John Joseph, 1921 and 1900s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1426)
    - Philip II of Spain (1527-1598), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1427)
    - Phipps, Constantine Henry, Second Earl of Mulgrave, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1428)
    - Piatt, N. A., 1800s, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1429)
      Images includes an original signature.
      Illustration is a nineteenth century letterpress halftone.
    - Pickens, Andrew, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1430)
    - Pierce, Franklin, 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M1431)
    - Pierce, Ovid Williams, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1432)
    - Pierce, Ovid Williams, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1433)
    - Pike, Albert, 1890s, (card photograph) (Folder M1434)
      Transferred from the C. C. Clay Mss.
    - Pillow, Gideon Johnson, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1435)
    - Pilmore, Joseph, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1436)
      This folder also contains a returned proof of the engraving.
    - Pinchot, Cornelia Elizabeth (Bryce), 1900s, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 silhouette) (Folder M1437)
      Transferred from the Harry A. Slattery papers.
      Silhouette removed to Box LG03, Folder OV141 in the Oversize Subseries. This image was used by Mrs. Pinchot in her campaign for a seat in Congress.
    - Pinchot, Gifford, 1900-1909 and 1900s, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1438.1)
      Transferred from the Henry A. Slattery papers.
    - Pinchot, Gifford, 1925 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1438.2)
    - Pinckney, Charles Cotesworth, 1862 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1439)
    - Pinckney, Thomas, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1440)
    - Pinker(?), Ralph, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1441)